Walk
Walking
Walking like
Walking like a
Walking like a man
Walking like a man on
Walking like a man on stilts
I'm
I'm fall
I'm falling
I'm falling o
I'm falling over
Walk
Walking
Walking like
Walking like a
Walking like a man
Walking like a man on
Walking like a man on stilts
Oh
Oh my
Oh my, oh
Oh my, oh my
Oh my, oh my, oh
Oh my, oh my, oh my
You
You got
You got me
Oh
Oh my
Oh my, oh
Oh my, oh my
Oh my, oh my, oh my
You
You got
You got me
You got me, yah
You got me, yah-ah
Ta
Taking
Taking it
Taking it slow
Fo
Follow
Follow the
Follow the flow
Ma
Making
Making it
Making it, ma
Making it, making
Making it, making it
Making it, making it, ma
Making it, making it, making
Making it, making it, making it
Ma
Making
Making it
Making it rain
Making it rain now
Ma
Making
Making it
Making it, ma
Making it, making
Making it, making it
Ma
Making
Making it
Making it rain
Hah!
One
One does
One does for
One does for won
One does for wonder
Won
Wonder
Wonder and
Wonder and light
Could
Couldn't
Couldn't you
Couldn't you be
Couldn't you be my
Couldn't you be my guar
Couldn't you be my guardi
Couldn't you be my guardian
To
Toni
Toni-ni
Toni-ni-ni
Toni-ni-ni-night?
I
I ne
I never
I never knew
I never knew love
I never knew love un
I never knew love until
When
When you
When you found
When you found m
When you found my
Found
Found my
Found my heart
Found my heart on
Found my heart on the
Found my heart on the out
Found my heart on the outside
Ta
Taking
Taking it
Taking it slow
Fo
Follow
Follow the
Follow the flow
Ma
Making
Making it
Making it, ma
Making it, making
Making it, making it
Ma
Making
Making it
Making it rain
Making it rain now
Ma
Making
Making it
Making it, ma
Making it, making
Making it, making it
Ma
Making
Making it
Making it rain